This is the story ******One in 2009...
这是关于两场相亲约会的故事: 一次是在2009年...
And one seven years earlier.
另一次是在7年前
In all that time, my dating routine remained more or less the same...
这些年来 我的约会总还是老三篇...
until the fall of 2009, when I finally had a date that was different.
直到2009年秋 我总算有一场不落俗套的约会了
Because it was exactly the same.
因为这次完全是毫无二致
I was on a blind date with the same woman I went on a blind date with seven ars earlier.
我约的正是7年前约会过的那个女人
- Ted? - Jen?
It's nice to meet you.
见到你很高兴
And she didn't remembeit. But then again...
她对我毫无印象 同样的...
It's nice to meet you,too.
我也是
Neither did
我也不记得她
- Do you want to... - Yeah.
- 我们 走吧... - 嗯
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 饭粘子 Holah   校对: 葱家的小毛毛 时间轴: 咔肉肉
How I Met Your Mother Season05 Episode02
老爸老妈罗曼史 第五季 第2集
Guess whjust got four tickets to the "Origins of Chewbacc" Star Wars exhibit?
猜猜谁搞到4张"楚巴卡起源" 星战展的票子了?
Why?
为什么?
- No,I said,"Guess who?" - I heard u.
- 不 我问的是"猜猜谁" - 我听到了
Yeah,um,isn't it a little early in our relationship to do something that would end our relationship?
现在就做会让咱俩掰了的事儿 是不是早了点啊?
What? No,what are you talking about? It can be our first double date as couples!
什么? 说什么呢? 这会是我们首次4人一起约会
And plus, it sounds awesome!
而且 听着很过瘾啊!
Is the original Chewbacca going to be there?
楚巴卡的首演演员会到场吗?
Peter Mayhew,in the fur. Who's with me?
Peter Mayhew 穿戏服的哦 谁跟我一起去?
Hey,do you think they'll have Wookiee to Engsh dictionaries there?
嘿 你说词典里会加上"猿人"这词条不?
I mean,even just an everyday phrase book would be helpful.
就算是常用短语集也好啊
We're not going to the "Origins of Chewbacca" exhibit,Marshall.
Marshall 我们不去"楚巴卡起源"展
It's in Houston this year. Everyone knows that.
今年是在休斯顿 大家都知道
I just wanted to get rid of the girls.
我只是想甩了那俩娘们儿罢了
Where are you taking me,Barney?
Barney 你带我去哪儿?
This wasn't the first time your Uncle Barney
这可不是你们Barney叔叔头回绑架我们了
Wait a second.
慢着
The "Origins of Chewbacca" exhibit's in Montreal this year.
"楚巴卡起源"展今年是在蒙特利尔
Everyone knows that. Where are you taking me?
大家都知道 你带我去哪儿?
My guy in thDA's office scored us front row seats to a lethainjection.
地方检察官一哥们儿给我们搞到了 注射死刑前排观赏的票子
But wee still stopping for chili dogs first.
不过 我们还是会先买辣热狗的
Stop the cab.
停车
Wherare you taking me?
你要带我去哪儿?
Barney, why are we here?
Barney 我们来这儿干嘛?
Marsll,now that Robin and I are together,
Marsll 我现在和Robin在一起
I've learned a lot about relationships by watching you and Lily.
通过你和Lily的言传身教 我学到了很多
Thanks,man.
谢了 伙计
You're a terrible couple.
你俩糟透了
Lily has taken all the man out of you.
Lily把你身上的男子气概全榨干了
I used to think that's just every relationship.
我还以为大家都像你们这样
But what've got with Robin proves that you can have a girlfriend
但跟Robin在一起后 发现原来交女朋友
and fully functioning male genitalia all at the se time.
也不妨碍你寻花问柳的
Okay,right. So,if Robin knew that you were here, she would be completely fine with it?
好 就是说如果Robin知道你在这儿 她也完全可以接受的咯?
Are you kidding?
开什么玩笑?
She'd sprint down here with a purse full of singles and a poncho for the 10:30 Jell-O show.
她会带着装满票子的钱包冲来 还不忘为10点半的果冻摔跤秀带雨披来
BT-Dub,I lled ahead-- it's lime.
顺便 先声明 是酸橙口味的
Meanwhile,Jen and I were my favorite first date restauran. for the second time.
与此同时 在我首次约会最爱去餐厅里 我和Jen在进行第二次约会
So,Jen,what do you do?
那么 Jen 你是做什么的?
I'm between jobs-- banking cris.
还在找工作 银行业危机嘛
I'm between jobs-- Internet bubble burst.
还在找工作 互联网泡沫经济嘛
Makes me reaze I should go into something more stable... like banking.
我觉得我该去找个更稳定的活儿... 像是银行业什么的
So what about you?
那你是做什么的?
I'm an architect.
我是个建筑师
Hopefully,one d, I can use my own humble brush onhe masterpiece that is Manhattan's skyline.
希望终有一日 我这个小小粉刷匠 可以在曼哈顿的天际留下一篇杰作
I teach aritecture.
我是教建筑的
Get 50% off ******
买书可以打五折 所以还挺好的
Married!
已婚人士!
What is wrong with you? You're just looking.
你咋回事儿啊? 只是看看啊
It's like fantasing about other women.
就像是幻想别的女人一样
It's harmless.
人畜无害
Wa. Don't tell me you don't fantasize about other won.
等下 你不会不幻想别的女人吧
I do!
我幻想的!
- It's just not that easy. - False.
- 只是没那么容易罢了 - 扯淡
I once fantasized abt that silhouette chick you see on a truck's mudflaps.
我都幻想过你在卡车挡泥板上瞧见的 那个像小妞的泥巴影子
Took me less than a mile.
我想了快1英里呢
Not everyone is you, okay,Barney?
不是人人都像你 好吧 Barney?
Even when I do start to have a dirty thought like that...
就算我开始有这种坏坏的念头...
it seems so much like cheating on Lilythat I feel guilty
那种像是背叛Lily念头让我充满罪恶感
So first,I need to have a different fantasy.
所以 首先 我得先幻想别的
Banews. Lily has a rare and fatal hiccup disorder that's apparently medicalllegitimate.
坏消息 Lily得了一种罕见且致命的 打嗝失调症 医学上来说 是合理存在的
What? How could this be?
什么? 怎么可能?
Beats me,but it says it ght here on this doctor clipboard that doctors have.
问倒我了 但医生的专用写字夹板上 是这么说的
(6个月后)
It time,baby.
时候到了 宝贝儿
I will never love again.
我再也不会爱上别人了
No,Marshall,yomust.
不 Marshall 你得学会爱上别人
And afr an appropriate number of years, you should find someone else.
数年之后 你会遇见别人的
Someone like that busty delivery girl from thaone time.
像那天那个豪乳的送货女郎一般的人
And plow her like a cornfield.
像开垦玉米地一般去开垦她吧
And so,Marshall, honor Lily, you must find that busty delivery girl from that e time
Marshall 要谨记Lily的话 必需找到那天的那位豪乳送货女郎
and plow her like a cornfiel
像开垦玉米地一般去开垦她
******
数年之后...
Delivery for Marshall Eriksen.
Marshall Eriksen的快递
******
这记吻是给你的 Lil
Where do I sign?
我签哪儿?
And then watch out, because it is on!
然后请小心 因为太火辣了
at is the saddest thing I've ever heard.
这是我听过最可悲的故事了
Dude,Lily gets you in real life She has no business in your fantasies.
老兄 Lily在你现实生活的方方面面了 没理由让她在你的幻想里插一脚
It's all I know,okay? I can't,I can't help .
我都明白的 只是 只是我控制不住
I accept your invitation.
我接受你的邀请
Marshall Eriksen, from this day forward, I will be the wingman of your mind.
Marshall Eriksen 从今往后 我将是你思想的同伴
Now,focus on the next dancer.
现在 专心看下一位舞者
Put Lily completely out of your mind.
脑子里丝毫别去想Lily
Gentlemen, say hello J-J-J-Jasmine.
先生们 有请J-J-J-Jasmine
Barney?
it just me or does that stripper look exactly like...
是我眼花了 还是那舞娘长的跟...
Ted,we found a stripper who looks exactly like Lily!
Ted 我们见到个长的 跟Lily一模一样的脱衣舞娘
- Yeah,I can't talk right now. - I'm speechless,too.
- 好 现在不方便说话 - 我也无语了
Everything's as perky as we've always imagined!
和我们总幻想的一模一样!
Stop looking at her.
别盯着她了
Uh,look,I got to go. Take a picture.
我要挂了 拍张照哦
Oh,I will.
会拍的
But first,I'm going make Marshall watch as I wedge Ulysses S. Grant between his wife's tatas.
但我要先让Marshall看着我把50大洋 塞到他老婆的咪咪罩里去
I'll kill you!
我要宰了你!
- Sorry about that. - So,any thoughts on food?
- 不好意思 - 想好点什么了没?
******
嗯 想跟我来份牡蛎吗?
- I woullove to share the oysters. - Good.
- 很乐意和你来份牡蛎 - 好的
'Cause if you didn't... that would be mighty shellfish.
因为要是你不喜欢的话... 那就太"治湿"了  (贝壳类的意思 又与自私发音相同)
Wow,that's bad.
喔 那可不好
That's why it's funny!
这才是笑点!
*******
咱俩以前约会过
We've been on this exact blind date before.
我们俩以前约会过
In this exact same restaurant.
就在这同一家餐厅
Correct me if I'm wrong,
我要是说错了你纠正我 我记得上次约会结果不大好
Meneither.
我也记得是
I remember thinking that you were a little snobby.
我还觉得你有点势利来着
it,you... You dress ur cats up in weird costumes.
慢着 你给你家的猫穿奇怪的衣服来着
ey're not weird. See,you're being snobby again.
有什么怪的 看 你又势利了
Oh,my God. Do you realize what this means?
哦 天哪 知道这意味着什么吗?
Since our first da, we've done a complete lap of all the sgle people in New York
从上次约会之后 我们把纽约单身男女兜了遍
only to enup back here, with each other.
结果蓦然回首 咱俩又聚首了
We're going to die alone, aren't we?
我们要孤老终生了 是吗?
Well,you've got your cats.
你至少还有你的猫嘛
This is insane.
太疯狂了
Wait,I got to a. Why did you think I was snobby?
我想问一下 为什么你觉得我势利?
Wait... Okay... yeah,weere siing over there...
等等... 我们当时坐那张桌
MainLobster. They spelled "Main" without the "e."
主角龙虾 缅因少写了个e (Maine 写成了Main)
Good to know we're not getting the crappy understudy lobsters,right?
很好 我们吃的不是蹩脚的替补龙虾 对不?
Tonight,the role of pound-and-a-half lobster will be played by...
今晚一磅半重的龙虾一角色将由...
I get it,Ted.
我懂 Ted
inting out spelling errors in a menu makes you seem kind of snooty.
对菜单上的拼写错误揪着不放 你有点妄自尊大了
- I had no idea. - Okay,well,what about me?
- 完全没意识到 - 好了 那我呢?
Aside from the cats, how did I come across?
除了猫的事之外 我还有哪儿做的不好?
That's right-- the check.
对了 结账
Thcheck came and,of course, I was going to pay, but you didn't do the check dance.
账单来了 当然 我是会买单的 但你没跟我来抢着买单
Guys want to wave the girl off and,you know, look like a big shot.
小伙子们总是想和姑娘抢着付账 像是个款爷一样
I had no idea.
我没意识到
This is good. We're learning stuff. You know what we should do?
很好 我们学到了 有进步了 知道我们该做什么吗?
We should retrace the rest of that night and figure out what se we do wrong on first dates.
我们该循着当年那晚的脚步 重游故地 看看我们第一次约会还有哪儿做错了
'Cause let's be honest-- we are scaring people off,Jen.
说实话吧 我们把别人都吓跑了 Jen
We really are. Okay,I'm in.
可不是么 好 我同意
- Great. - Where'd we go next?
- 好 - 下面去哪儿?
- I think we went to MacLaren's. - Okay.
- 去了MacLaren's酒吧 - 好的
Hey,I didn't really talk about my cats that much,did I?
嘿 关于我的猫 我没谈个没完吧?
And then, thers Tabby-gail Adams, the jester of the group.
然后 是虎皮猫Adams 它真是它们当中的小丑
Tone down the kitty talk. Check.
猫的事少说 了解了
You will not believe who we saw tonight.
你们不会相信我们今晚见到谁了
- Dude,um... - We saw the third doppelganger!
- 兄弟 别... - 我们见到了第三个复制体!
I should explain.
我解释一下
Over the years we had spotted two stngers who looked exactly like membs of our group.
这些年来 我们见过两个人 与我们之中的人长得一摸一样
Lesbian Robin.
拉拉Robin
And Moustache Marshall.
还有胡子Marshall
By the folwing summer, we would find the remaining two doppelgangers.
接下来的夏天  剩下的两个复制体会陆续出现
But I'll get to that.
不过这以后再说
Ladies,meet Stripper Lily.
女士们 有请脱衣女郎Lily
Yeah,I couldn't get her face in it.
嗯 没拍到脸
But she looks just like you.
可她真的跟你长得一摸一样
So you went to a strip club?
你们去了脱衣舞夜总会?
Busted.
被发现了
And there was a stripper o looked exactly like me?
而那里有个脱衣女郎长得跟我一摸一样?
Okay,babe,look, before you get mad,let me...
宝贝 别生气 我解释...
Awesome! I bet the guys were going crazy.
帅呀! 我想男人们肯定都爽疯了
Oh,I bet th wanted to touch her so bad.
他们被撩动的欲火焚身
But all you can do is look, unless you go into the back room,but honey, you got to pay for that.
可只能眼看手勿动 除非你带她去里屋 不过得付钱呀
So... Strip club.
话说...脱衣舞夜总会
Marshall made me go.
Marshall逼我去的
All right,so whatdid I do Let me have it. I'here to learn.
接下来我做错了什么  告诉我 我学着呢
****but you didn't offer me your jacket.
嗯 聊天的时候我暗示感觉很冷 可你没有把外套披给我
It's a little brisk out tonight,huh?
今晚有点凉风飕飕哦 是吧?
- Not really. - Really? I cat feel my fingers.
- 没啥感觉 - 真的? 我手指都没知觉了
I'm pretty impervis to stuff like that.
我还挺扛得住
I couldn't admit I was cold.
我可不能承认自己冷啊
I didn't want to seem like a wimp compared to your action hero ex-boyfriend
相比你整天挂在嘴边动作巨星般的前男友
who you wouldn't stop talking about.
我可不想显得弱不禁风
After a day of fighting fires, Jim would love to come home a unwind working on his '68 Camo.
在一天的救火工作之后  Jim喜欢捣腾他的68版Camero作为放松
That or bare-knuck boxing, which he learned in the Marine Corps.
又或者不带拳套打打拳击  他在海军陆战队学的
I had an aunt in the Cst Guard.
我有个阿姨是海岸巡逻队队员
Okay,so no talking about the ex.
好吧 不谈前男友
Not even about his shocngly small wiener?
即使他的JJ超小也不谈?
See? Why didn't you lead off with that?
你瞧? 为啥你不先说说这个呢?
Was there a shower on stage?
舞台上会不会有花洒?
Sometimes there's a shower on stage.
舞台上要是有花洒
I bet ripper me would get in there with another girl and just gbananas.
我想脱衣女郎Lily和另一个女孩 会跳进去一起放纵
See,Marshall?We got to have a bros' night at a strip club
你瞧 Marshall?  咱们去夜总会搞个兄弟之夜
and both of our dies are totally cool with it.
而咱们的女人完全不介意
I'm not cool with it.
我很介意
Because they understand that it's healthy for us to do that from time to time.
因为她们知道有时放纵一下 对我们是有好处的
It's disgusting.
是非常恶心的
Because it's harmless.
因为这无伤大雅
Did one of your whores tell you that?
哪个妓女跟你这么说的?
And,Lil,Marshall shouldn't have to go to so much trouble just to have an innocent fantasy.
还有Lil Marshall幻想一下而已 不需要这么麻烦的
Trouble? What trouble?
麻烦? 什么麻烦?
It's,no,it's nothing.
没事 没事
Marshall,tell her. We're all friends re.
Marshall 告诉她 这里都是好朋友
No,we're not.
我们不是
Sometimes I think about other women.
有时我会对其他女人有幻想
Okay,it happens But even when I do, I feel so guilty that I-I have to imagine you...
但即使我这么做 我会很内疚 以至于我会先幻想...
passing away first, *****You're...
你先过世了 因为即使是幻想  我也不想背叛你 你...
u're just my life,baby. And I love you.
你是我的唯一 我爱你
You kill me f?
你把我弄死了?
I mean,fantasize about other rls all you want, but could you maybe not murder me?
幻想其他女人就算了 可能不能别谋杀我?
Murder? No! I,baby-no. You develop a chronic illness!
谋杀? 不是这样的!  你患了一种慢性病!
I are no expense for your care! We're,like,this close to a cure.
我无微不至地照顾你! 我还以你的名字 设立了基金会 你差点就能治好了
Remember?
记得吗?
Oh,yeah! I do remember.
是啊! 我当然记得
We went in here for a drink with your friends. Who I loved...Or hated,
我们在里面和你的朋友喝酒 我很喜欢他们...或者很讨厌他们
depending on whether you'r still friends with them.
取决于你们还是不是朋友
- You loved them. - They're familyTed.
- 我很喜欢他们 - 他们就像家人 Ted
Let's go in and se what they remember.
进去看看他们还记得你不
And they are my best fends, so don't be surprised if they suddenly "can't think" anything I do wrong.
还有他们是我的好朋友  要是把我描述成圣人 别太惊讶
Did he juggle? Bapuns?
他喜欢耍宝吗? 喜欢说冷笑话?
Expect a standing ovation for picking up a $19 check
还是会为了捡到19美金的支票 而得意忘形
Oh,let's not forget the menu typo gold mine.
别忘了菜单纠错小金矿
Keep pannin' that river,buddy.
哼哧哼哧的淘金呢 伙计
Well,it is a lot cheaper than buying a coom.
还不够买一套套呢
Actuallyyou know what it was?
事实上 知道吗?
I remember him coming across as kinof a player.
我当时觉得他是个花花公子
- Me? - Ted?
- 我? - Ted?
Yeah. We were all sitting over there...
对 那时我们坐那边...
And here's a picture of my cats dressed up like Batman villains.
这些是我的猫 cosplay蝙蝠侠里恶棍的扮相
You got the Joker, the Riddler,Mr. Freeze...
有小丑 谜语客 急冻人...
Wh about Cat Woman?
猫女呢?
Yeah,that would've been good.
对哦 那样更好
Ted!
Nice.
不错哦
Wait,wait,wait,no,no,no! I member that.******
等等 不对! 我记得了 我不是在看女孩
Psst,Ted.
Ted
Nice.
不错哦
We were checking out Moustache Marshall.
那时我们在看胡子Marshall
Gosh,I thought you were such a jerk. I'm so sorry.
天 我还以为你是个色鬼呢 对不起
Yeah,well, it's ne to know "past me" wasn't a total jackass,huh?
得知"以前的我"没这么混蛋 不错吧?
"Present you" isn't so bad,eier.
"现在的你"也很不错
Thank you very much.
谢谢
Oh,yeah! I rember this.
是哦! 我记得了
and there's the Chrysler Building.
那是克莱斯勒大楼
And the Empire State Building.
那是帝国大厦
And at 12:00, a rotund couple going at it against the glass.
十二点钟方向  一对矮胖情侣靠着玻璃抵死缠绵
That's kind of sweet.
真甜蜜
Oh,look. Snack break.
噢 开始吃零食了
Good for them.
他们可真行
Letting a guy eat pizza off your back,that's love.
后入式时还让那男的吃比萨 这就是爱呀
So,um...
那么
I knowhis wasn't the best first date of all time, but,uh,I'm glad we stuck it out.
我知道这不是个好的初次约会  不过我们能坚持下来 我很开心
Me,too.
我也是
That was really great. Wh... What went wrong?
那时感觉不错 后来是什么出了差错?
I member now.
我想起来了
Yeah.
So would you maybe,um... want to go out again?
或者 呃... 下次你还会跟我出来吗?
Yeah,I,I would. Will you call me?
我很愿意 你会打给我吗?
Absolutely.
当然
- Promise? - Promise.
- 保证? - 保证
I have beeso busy.
我一直以来都很忙
Good night,Ted.
晚安 Ted
Hello?
喂?
Jen,I sorry.Look,I know I'm seven years late with this call,
Jen 对不起 我知道这电话迟了七年
but I was an idiot back then.
但我以前是个白痴
You saw the goatee.
你也见到我的山羊胡子了
The truth is, I had a great time tonight, and I'd love to see you again.
说真的 我今晚过得很开心 我想再见到你
Ted,there are two kinds of guys.
Ted 这世界有两种男人
The guys that you want to call you,ho don't;
一种你想他打给你 却没打
and the guys you don't want to calyou,who always do.
另一种你不想他打给你 却老是打过来
And somehow, right now,you're both.
而现在 你两者皆是
Baby...
宝贝...
You should be able to fantasize about another woman without feeling guilty,
你对别的女人产生幻想不需要内疚
****
或者 呃... 不需要弄死我
I wishhat I could, but I've been doing this for so long, I'm all confused about death and sex.
我也想啊 但一直以来我都是这么做 已经在死亡和性爱间迷失了
It's gotten to the pot where every time I drive past a cemetery, I'm sportin' a partial.
现在我每次开车经过公墓 都会性奋
All right, we got to fix this.
好吧 我们来解决这问题
Okay,when Stripper Lily gets out here, you have my rmission to fantasize about her.
当脱衣女郎Lily出来之后  我允许你对她幻想
And since she's basically me, maybe you won't feel guilty.
既然她跟我一摸一样 或者你不会内疚
Than,baby. I'm-I'm so lucky I have you. And stripper you.
宝贝谢谢你 有你真好 还有脱衣女郎版的你
Bring out Strier Lily!
脱衣女郎Lily快出场!
- You know,I don't come here that much. - Hey,Barney.
- 我不怎么来这里的 - 嘿 Barney
He's the usual and I'll send over the other usual as soon as s's done stretching.
照例来一杯 等你性奋之后 我再照例给你上其他的
Thank you,kindly stranger.
谢谢你 善良的陌生人
Ladies and gentlemen... Oh,hey,Barney. Didn't see you come in.
女士们先生们... 嘿 Barney 来了哈
I' load up some AC/DC for you,buddy.
今晚给你选了些AC/DC乐队的曲子
Ladies and gentlemen,please******
女士们先生们 请热烈鼓掌 有请J-J-J-Jasmine
- I am hot! - Ye.
- 我真性感! - 是啊
Oh,crawl for it, stripper me. is is awesome.
给我爬 脱衣女郎版的我 这太帅了
Baby,can I get another hundred?
再给我一百好吗?
- That was a hundred? - Wow,she crawls fast.
- 你刚扔了一百? - 挖无 她爬得可真快
Look,Jen, I wish I could go back and talk some sense into 2002 Ted,
Jen 我真想回到2002年  教育教育自己
but that guy's a lost cause. He's 24.
可那家伙注定要失败 他才24
He thinks a little facial hair makes him look like John Depp.
他以为留点胡须就是强尼戴普了
And he has no idea what a great girl he's missing out on.
他不知道自己错过了多么好的女孩
But I've learned a lot since then.
但自从那时我学会了很多
ve learned a lot tonight.
今晚我也学到了很多
is that,seven years ago, it was mistake for us to go out.
七年前的约会是场错误 才是我们学到的
And I guess it was a mistake fous to go out tonight.
我想今晚的约会也是场错误
No,it wasn't. had a great time tonight.
不 不是的 我今晚很开心
And seven years ago, if you think abo it, we didn't miss by that much.
而七年前 仔细想想 其实也没错到哪里去
If a couple thin had gone a little bit differently...
要是些小细节能有所改变...
who knows what would have happened?
会发生什么 谁知道呢?
* Asking you to stay
* 开口留住你
* The words are finally here
* 终于说出口
* Let's rewind
* 让我们倒带重来
* And rind
* 倒带重来
* You see you're the only star
* 你是唯一的巨星
* In the film I never made
* 在没有我的电影里
* Would you rewd it all the time?
* 你会倒带重来吗?
* Rewind it all the time.
* 你回倒带重来吗?
You are the best.*******
你真棒 你真的太棒了
My girlfriend is at a strip club with me and she couldn't care less.
我的女朋友和我一起去夜总会 而她完全不介意
I do care,Barney. Look,we're dating now,okay? Th changes things.
我很介意 Barney  我们在拍拖 事态有所改变
We have to have a serious talk about this.
我们得好好谈谈这事
Just the best.
你真好
Girlfriend trouble?I wish I cou help,
女朋友耍脾气了? 我真希望能帮忙
but my unbelievably cool wife just bought us a private dance with her stripper body double.
但我完美的妻子刚付钱 想着与她的复制体一起单独给我跳舞
So if you need me, I'll be getting grinded like some pepper, in the Champagneoom.
需要我的话 去香槟间找我 会发现我被蹂躏的像被碾碎的胡椒粉
Just the best.
真好
now what?
现在怎么了?
- I justemembered why I didn't call you. - Why?
- 我刚记起为什么我没打给你了 - 为什么?
I can't believe I'm gonna screw this up again,but,um...
我这次竟然又要搞砸了 不过 嗯...
- I like finding typos in menus. - What?
- 我喜欢找出菜单里的错误 - 什么?
And I know my shellfish punis stupi but the truth ...
我知道我的贝壳笑话很蠢 可...
I'm not suddenly gonna stop making stupid jokes.
我很难突然不讲冷笑话
Now that you mention i.
既然你这么说
I'm never going to stop talking about my cats.
我也很难不谈我的猫
They're funny and adorable and totally worth having to take six Benadryl a day.
它们真的很可爱  绝对值得我每天吃六颗盐酸苯海拉明 (治过敏鼻炎 她对猫过敏)
Shouldn't we hold out for the person who doesn't just tolerate our little quirks,
我们应该要等的人  应该是会不仅仅会包容我们的怪癖
but actually kind of likes them?
而且还会喜欢它们的 对吗?
Even if it means finding ourselves on another blind date with each other,seven years from now?
即使我们沦落到在七年后的另一次 相亲中相遇 还要寻找下去 是吗?
Oh,dear God, I hope that don't happen.
老天 我希望不要吧
Well... good luck out there,Jen.
祝你好运 Jen
You too,Ted.
你也是 Ted
You'll find your shellfish lady.
你会找到你的贝壳女生的
And kids,when I told your mother that shellfish joke, she did laugh.
孩子 当我跟你们母亲说贝壳笑话时 她笑了
And I swear,it was only, like,30% pity.
我敢说 那只有30%是同情分
Hey,Lil. Looks like,uh,Jasmine's having a hard time getting out of those boots.
嘿 Lil 看来Jasmine脱靴子遇到麻烦了
What did you say,buddy?
兄弟你说啥?
- Lily? - Who?
- Lily? - 说?
Oh,yes... I am this Lily.
呃 对... 我素Lily
We married long time.
咱们婚了好久了
May I have monies for shopping?
给我钱购物好不?
Lily!